

# CONTACT

https://pariola.dev

🚡 Lagos, Nigeria, Africa

#### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF TECH: METALLURGY TECHNOLOGY.

Oct 2018 - Feb 2023

Federal University of Technology, Minna.

# **OTHERS**

**PWAs** 

Figma

Design Systems

SE Optimization

**Build Automation** 

Shopify Theme Customization

# KEHINDE OMOPARIOLA

Creative Front-end engineer

## **ABOUT**

Meet Kehinde Omopariola, a highly productive Frontend Engineer with over two years of experience in building pixel-perfect user interfaces. He is a fast and flexible learner who designs with an eye for detail and a commitment to creating fluid user experiences.

Omopariola has a wealth of experience developing JavaScript applications and strives for performance and scalability. He is a valuable asset to any team and delivers top-quality results.

#### FRONTEND TECHNOLOGIES

Reactjs CSS Preprocessing

Nextjs Gsap
JavaScript (ES6 Hands-on) Mocha

Framer-motion

HTML5 & CSS3 Vuejs

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## FRONTEND ENGINEER (FREELANCE)

Regnify Softwares | Oct 2020 - Present.

- Converted user interfaces from Figma to PX perfect codes
- Rebuilt and Redesigned most pages owned by the company.
- Created an inventory management web application and performed the role of a sole front-end engineer utilizing using HTML, SCSS, and React.
- Created an event management web application and performed the role of a sole front-engineer utilizing using Reactjs.

#### FRONTEND ENGINEER

Klas INC | May 2021 - Present

- Converted user interfaces from Figma to PX perfect codes
- Rebuilt major landing pages with the company's official stack.
- Built dynamic and marketing-focused mail templates on SendGrid.

## FRONTEND ENGINEER (FREELANCE)

Diool | April 2022 - Present

- Worked closely with the growth team to help integrate tools that analyze user behaviors on our product
- Revamped the whole website design and page structure to give it satisfying UX
- Converted the existing website into Next.js for smooth SE Optimization on our site

